http://www.sweaterbabe.com/privacy/

Loading... Please wait...
My Account
Wish Lists
Sign in or Create an account
View Cart
Join our mailing listto get NEW pattern announcements, FREE pattern offers, and more!
Our Newsletter
Sign up for FREE pattern offers, new pattern announcements, & much more!
Privacy Policy
We have created this Policy in order to clearly communicate our firm commitment to your privacy.This Policy is applicable to all services provided by Katherine Lee, SweaterBabe.com and all their related parties, including but not limited to affiliates, agents, partners, consultants, staff, members, advertisers, or owners, related websites or businesses (collectively "SweaterBabe" or "we" or "us"). SweaterBabe reserves the right to change this Policy at any time.
Using our websites demonstrates your consent to SweaterBabe's collection and use of information pursuant to this Policy, and continued use of this site following the posting of changes to this Policy will signify your acceptance of such changes. This Policy governs the use of your name, e-mail address, payment information, and similar personal information that you may provide SweaterBabe in the course of using our website, products or services.If you received communications from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us or one of our affiliated companies. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.If you would like to be removed from the mailing list that was used to contact you, please simply follow the "unsubscribe" instructions that were in the email you received.SweaterBabe Uses Cookies. SweaterBabe collects certain information about how website visitors and users use our websites by using technology called "cookies", which are bits of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies can enhance your online experience by automatically saving your preferences. We use cookies because they help us to provide you a better online experience. The information we collect through the use of cookies allows SweaterBabe to know when and for how long you logged on to the SweaterBabe website, so that we can try to understand how to better serve your needs. If you object to the use of cookies for any reason, you may set your Internet browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept it. If, however, you decline to receive cookies, you may have difficulty in using certain features of this site.SweaterBabe Collects Personal Information. We collect personal information in order to provide certain products and services to our customers. For example, if you: Place a product order: SweaterBabe will collect and use your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and credit card information to fulfill your order and provide follow up; Request promotional items or information: SweaterBabe will collect and use your name and address, or e-mail address to fulfill your request and provide follow up; Sign-up for any of our mailing lists or membership services: SweaterBabe will collect information from you in order to facilitate the publishing of that and other mailing lists and provide follow up; and Fill out a survey: SweaterBabe will store and use this information to learn more about our visitors and target future promotions to visitors that will be most interested in them. Information that you submit about yourself may be used by SweaterBabe to provide you requested services, communicate with you about our and related services, improve your online experience, or support our continuing efforts to offer you the information and services in which we believe you may be interested. SweaterBabe provides aggregate statistics and information about our sales, traffic patterns and related site information to third parties. We also reserve the right to share aggregate statistical data of which your personal information is a part, as well as your specific personal information with our affiliates, advertisers, and partners. You are responsible for checking this Policy periodically to monitor any changes to our data sharing practices.In addition, SweaterBabe may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your personal information when required to do so by law, when SweaterBabe, in its sole discretion believes that you have violated any state or federal laws, or SweaterBabe in its sole discretion deems it necessary or appropriate to protect the personal safety of other users of SweaterBabe services or to protect the rights or property of SweaterBabe.SweaterBabe E-mail Announcements and Newsletters. SweaterBabe and its affiliates use e-mail to send announcements regarding new products, services, and/or promotions, and informational newsletters that would be of interest to our audience. You can choose to unsubscribe to any of our emails by using the unsubscribe instructions in the emails or by emailing us. SweaterBabe will also send replies to customer e-mail inquiries via e-mail. Finally, if you have sent a request to SweaterBabe or any of our affiliates, advertisers or partners about which we need to communicate with you, we may do so by e-mail.Security is a Top Concern. Although SweaterBabe carefully selects third party service providers, affiliates and advertisers, is sensitive to the privacy and security of your personal information, and intends to safeguard such information, SweaterBabe and any such third parties cannot guarantee absolute security for such information. Such information may be transmitted through or using the Internet, other public telecommunications networks, servers, hardware and software ("systems") that are not owned, operated, or controlled by SweaterBabe. SweaterBabe makes no assurances that such information will remain private when stored in or transmitted through such systems or its own. Although we intend to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications are entirely secure. By using our Services you agree to indemnify and hold harmless SweaterBabe from any and all liability for any such failures in security and to pursue such third party service providers as designated by SweaterBabe instead.SweaterBabe Interactive Areas. SweaterBabe is not liable for information posted in Interactive Areas. Our web sites may provide interactive areas such as discussion forums to enhance the user experience and build communities around our products and services. You acknowledge that should you participate in such interactive areas, the information you voluntarily post about yourself and third parties in such areas might be accessed, collected and used by third parties outside of SweaterBabe. In addition, you may not post any defamatory, obscene, slanderous, or otherwise illegal material, or any material which infringes any third-party copyrights or other intellectual property rights on any interactive areas. Violators will be subject to termination of accounts and possible legal action. Although SweaterBabe employs security technology, it cannot guarantee complete security in personal websites or password-protected areas, and SweaterBabe will not be held liable for any user's or other visitor's disclosure of personal information on SweaterBabe or affiliated websites. DO NOT POST YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS OR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ON OUR WEB SITES.Submissions. If your activities on or related to our web sites result in your submission of written or other materials (including but not limited to emails, message board postings, photos, graphics, designs, video, music, software, recordings, articles, commentary, comments, etc.), such materials shall become the property of SweaterBabe. Such transfer of ownership shall include the broader of either a worldwide, perpetual, royalty-free license or the copyright and any and all other associated rights, such as moral rights. You agree that such transfer will allow SweaterBabe complete control and rights to reproduce, sell, modify, license, rent, giveaway, share, publish, create derivative works from, or otherwise distribute the materials in its sole discretion without notice or compensation to you.A Special Note about Children. SweaterBabe and its services are not directed to minors. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. IF YOU ARE UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE, YOU SHOULD NOT USE OUR SITES OR SERVICES.Disputes. SweaterBabe Privacy Policy disputes are handled by our customer service team with the highest concern for your privacy and satisfaction.SweaterBabe Links. SweaterBabe web sites may contain links to websites not owned or controlled by SweaterBabe. SweaterBabe is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such sites. Users accept all responsibility for their activities on our sites and services linked to from them.For further information about or to contact us, please visit the "About SweaterBabe" or "Contact Us & Help" sections of the Sites. If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent from us or purporting to be sent from us, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to us for review.
FeedWind
Store Links
About SweaterBabe
Contact Us & Help
Classes
Pattern Errata
Customer Testimonials
Knitting Abbreviations
Sweaterbabe.com. All Rights Reserved Worldwide.
Designed and developed by Supertron Infotech
SweaterBabe.com uses Constant Contact
